<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Assembly - Category - backwards.engineering</title>
        <link>https://psqnix.github.io/categories/assembly/</link>
        <description>Assembly - Category - backwards.engineering</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://psqnix.github.io/categories/assembly/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Reversing Hero</title>
    <link>https://psqnix.github.io/reveringhero/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://psqnix.github.io/reveringhero/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION ReversingHero is a Reverse Engineering self learning kit (x86_64 on linux) wrapped inside one binary file. It is made of 15 levels, with difficulty gradually increasing. Created by xoprd, this course can be found here : Reversing Hero
Here is just my attempt to solve the 15 levels.
 ▸ Reversing Hero 1  ▸ Reversing Hero 2 The following procedure shows a simple routine where there is a bit rotation.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>[Practical Binary Analysis]  Part.1 (Chapter.1)</title>
    <link>https://psqnix.github.io/practicalbinaryanalysis_part1/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://psqnix.github.io/practicalbinaryanalysis_part1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[As malware increasingly obfuscates itself and applies anti-analysis techniques to thwart our analysis, we need more sophisticated methods that allow us to raise that dark curtain designed to keep us out--binary analysis can help. The goal of all binary analysis is to determine (and possibly modify) the true properties of binary programs to understand what they really do, rather than what we think they should do. While reverse engineering and disassembly are critical first steps in many forms of binary analysis, there is much more to be learned.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>[Practical Binary Analysis] Introduction</title>
    <link>https://psqnix.github.io/practicalbinaryanalysis_intro/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://psqnix.github.io/practicalbinaryanalysis_intro/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[description: "What is Binary Analysis? This post covers the introduction of the book \"Practical Binary Analysis\" " As malware increasingly obfuscates itself and applies anti-analysis techniques to thwart our analysis, we need more sophisticated methods that allow us to raise that dark curtain designed to keep us out--binary analysis can help. The goal of all binary analysis is to determine (and possibly modify) the true properties of binary programs to understand what they really do, rather than what we think they should do.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Starting Point on HackTheBox (2020)</title>
    <link>https://psqnix.github.io/startingpoint2020/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://psqnix.github.io/startingpoint2020/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[* { box-sizing: border-box; } .zoom:hover{ cursor: -moz-zoom-in; cursor: -webkit-zoom-in; cursor: zoom-in; } .zoom:link { transition: transform .2s; margin: 0 auto; } .zoom:active { cursor: -moz-zoom-in; cursor: -webkit-zoom-in; cursor: zoom-in; -ms-transform: scale(2); /* IE 9 */ -webkit-transform: scale(2); /* Safari 3-8 */ transform: scale(2); position: absolute; z-index: 9999; }  INTRODUCTION (pdf)
This path is composed of 6 boxes in a way that later boxes use information (like credentials) gathered from the previous ones.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
